Rooney doodle Sonic the Hedgehog we are
one award happy they got to fight to the
death
well I'm about to tell you what will
happen this is soccer hey Chuck
versus Rooney doodle
in this video I'll be taking a look at
the skills the strengths and weaknesses
and the weaponry you see which of the
two of them will come out on top if they
have a father but before we begin how
about I gave you a little bit of insight
on who exactly these characters are
first off we've got Rooney doodle
their effective leader of his band the
doodle box his color scheme is blue much
like soccer Hedgehogs from Sonic
Underground in fact these similarities
don't just stop there nobody is this
color scheme blue and he's the leader of
the band but he is also the author of
three siblings and he is the guitarist
of the group two other things he says
with sake Hedgehog many fans myself
included has noticed these similarities
but hey what you're gonna do
when you make a shot as good as Sonic
Underground it's only natural that some
other Beach is gonna want to look at the
sky and say damn I'm gonna make a
show like that and make the main
character exactly Rock saga Hedgehog
however despite sharing so many
similarities with Sonic Rooney doodle
himself is a very unique and different
character from Sonic first of all Rooney
duel has shown to be one of the kindest
people in the entire world whenever
somebody's in trouble you can be damn
sure that rude you'll be the first one
there to show up and help anybody in
need this is much even Sonic who would
rather help himself then help anybody
unless it was one of his Serbs
however while this is one of his biggest
strengths this is also one of his
biggest weaknesses I highly doubt Rooney
doodle
has the heart to kill somebody in cold
blood however there isn't you see the
Rooney doodle himself isn't a savage on
the battlefield with this tall member
body
I'm sure he could take out just about
anybody that comes before him in fact no
matter what picture you're looking at or
what video you're watching Rooney duel
is always standing at
an extreme height Kanpur do anybody else
that's next to him
so because height is such a huge
advantage for somebody when you apply to
that I decided to do a bit of research
to see just how tall exactly is Rooney
doodle
now before I go into my findings I feel
they need to inform you Rooney
doodle has been played by a multitude of
people over the years whether it be in
the stage plays the cartoons or the TV
shows however to keep it continually I
will only be counting the Rooney doodle
from the TV show now Rooney do is actor
already stazon whopping 6 feet and 8
inches tall however to really emphasize
his height in the show he is wearing
pumped-up boots to make him stand at a
whopping 7 feet and 4 inches now when
you compare this to Sonic and sock on
ground who is officially said to be just
over three feet tall the size difference
is very very noticeable it's so
noticeable in fact that maybe just maybe
Rooney's extreme hop won't be such an
advantage after all maybe it will even
be a disadvantage at Sonic's ha it will
be quite the easy feat one-two punch
Rooney doodle in the balls Rooney is
quite agile however so it may be a bit
of time for soft to land a blow but
therein lies the problem is
Sonic physically capable of taking down
Rooney doodle
is he that physically strong this is why
I took upon myself to study these two
characters to find just how physically
strong these two are now to do this I
feel we're going to need to do some math
into this the average human can
punch with the force of 178 pounds
however while this applies to Rooney
doodle
this does not apply to Sonic Sonic is
about half of ruins height therefore we
must divide the pounds of force by two
making
eighty-nine now this is begs a question
with 89 pounds of force can Sonic really
do any reasonable damage to ruin a well
actually yes it takes only
roughly 25 pounds of force to break a
human bone however with that being the
4th behind south ponds that doesn't
take into account one thing his super
speed which is officially said to be
roughly seven hundred and sixty-five
miles prior and now that we know Sox top
run feet as well as the destructive
force behind his fist we can out Cabala
to see just how strong sock will he is
am I doing this we will multiply his run
speed similar 65 by his power to break a
bone 25 now this adds up to establish
19125 pounds of force coming from
suckfest
right into who knows big-ass balls I say
some big-ass balls cuz you gotta have
some if you got stem for that
because let's face it Ruiz balls are out
of here B if shotguns weren't blown is
like however suck super speed is
his only weapon he's also got his guitar
a guitar that could turn into a
gun
yeah you can't make this up and I
don't even gotta go into some math
bullshi do explain what's on the tile
well burn roars after all
because damage it has been shown a
multitude of occasion the socks on
github can't burn straight through metal
I mean Louise Gargas how to but what can
that do say music
[Music]
yeah I'm sorry Oni but there's just not
much you can do you just don't have
anything you can use as a weapon against
sock the Hedgehog